With the cooperation of Fukai Resort Gero Longest Raku, we are pleased to bring you another installment from Gero.
It has begun. Hachiman Gakuen!
Yay!
Here is Haruna Sakamoto of Team Shirt and Okurashiki.
Exciting! We are here in Gifu, Gifu, as part of the "Hacchamessyugakuen" school trip, In Gero City.
Yay!
We are having fun.
Last time, we had pudding while taking a footbath.
It was great.
But you know, Yuzuki. There's one more footbath I'm interested in.
There's more?
Isn't it great?
There's so many.
There's too many to choose from.
There's one in the back.
There's some kind of footbath where you can walk around.
It says. Walking well.
Yes, it says that you can walk well.
What does that mean?
Does it mean a long footbath?
Maybe the kind where you can walk in the footbath.
Oh, no, no, no.
I'm excited.
I'm just curious.
First time, first time.
I want to go.
Let's go.
Let's go!
Kinkong kankong!
Knock-knock-knock.
Ta-da! We're here!
We made it! Let's go!
Isn't this thing right behind us already? He's got the power to walk!
I don't know... the stones are so rugged...
Don't you think they have some kind of foot pressure effect?
It feels like that! Oh, it says so!
Walking a few laps will improve blood circulation, stimulate the soles of the feet, and relieve the feet and shoulders.
So it stimulates those things too.
Sounds really good for the body!
Let's try it!
Okay, I'll get ready.
Let's try the walking power!
I hate hot water more than sore feet.
Oh, I see! Well, how's it feel?
It's hot! But it feels so good!
It's hot! Oh, it's that hot?
What's the temperature?
It feels good!
Does it feel good? Okay, I'm going to go in with you.
Oh, this is so much better.
It's hot! But not unbearably hot!
It's hot! But it feels so good!
And the stone is big, so it doesn't hurt too much.
It stimulates me nicely!
Oh, hey, what's the matter?
Is it cold?
It's cold!
Cold?
You're really hard to be cold!
Why can't I have a hot one and a cold one?
I'm really hard to be cold?
I'm really cold!
What, like in a swimming pool?
Oh, no!
Yusuki, you're disgusting!
I really can't! Is it cold? What do you mean?
It's cold! Let's walk faster! Help me! It's cold!
It's cold! That's cold water!
Wait a minute! It's really cold!
It's cold! It's cold! It's cold!
Warm!
It said "Warm!
It's so warm!
Hot! Hot! Hot!
Cold! Cold! Cold!
You know, this is like icing, isn't it?
After a gig.
It itches, you know, when the circulation gets better.
I don't know...
Hot! Hot! Hot!
Hot! It's so hot!
Icing effect!
The cold water is not working!
But!
It's the icing!
It's really improving circulation.
My feet are getting really itchy.
Oh, my God!Great!
That's great!
Huh!
Mmm!
Come on!
Huh!
That's cold!
It's better than before!
Wait a minute! I really hate cold water!
I can't!
The water is cold, cold!
But I've been saying this for a while...
It's cold.
Maybe it'll work.
Wow, that's great!
It's like... It's like a Buddha feeling.
This way, this way is good. This way is heaven.
Oh, it's cold!
It feels so good!
But, you know, I keep spinning.
It feels so good.
Cold water and hot water.
Okay, here we go.
Cold and warm will improve circulation.
It definitely improves circulation.
Oh, this is really, really good.
It's really good, but it feels really good, so you guys should try it.
Let's get really healthy together here.
There's a lot of history about hot springs, and there's a lot of stuff in there, too.
It's a museum.
I'm going to study after this!
Next is the Frog Shrine.
Frog!
Puke puke puke!
Because they are vomitous?
Because it's vomit, it's a frog.
Vomit vomit vomit
Frogs are really full of vomit.
Frogs are all over the place. They're cute, but...
Frog shrine
Hey, hey, hey, here.
The windows are frogs, too.
Did you see it?
Aren't they cute?
It's cute.
It's the perfect shade of green.
It's like a hidden frog. It's everywhere.
Like hidden frogs.
Everything is green.
Is this where you get your water?
It's so cute.
They're all frogs.
Thank you very much.
Wow!
It's the Frog Great Myojin!
If you make a monetary donation, you can hear a message from the Frog Great Myojin.
I want to hear it!
I'll go then
Thank you very much. You'll be flush with money from now on.
Please be careful on your way home
You spoke.
Wait a minute. There was a time difference.
I've never had someone talk to me while I was praying.
I was a little surprised,
He said, "Money is overflowing.
He said, "May you be overflowed with money.
And I was so surprised that I forgot to ring this.
Oh, that's right.
I'll ring it at the end.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. May you be filled to overflowing.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Have a safe trip home.
May the money flow in.
Thank you very much.
Yes.
Yes. I've made the rounds.
Senbakumonokan and Frog Shrine.
How was it?
The ability to walk on foot
It's so new.
It's new, isn't it?
The water was pretty hot and the water was pretty cold.
My legs felt so light.
It's really different.
It's really different. The weight is different.
So, after walking a lot in GeroSo, after walking a lot in the streets of Gero
I thought it would be a great way to end the day.
I thought it would be a great idea.
I agree.
How was the Frog Shrine?
I would like you to visit there as a set,
After all, you have been so kind to us.
Thank you very much.
You told me.
You wrote it right on the side.
It said you could hear the Frog Great Goddess speak to you.
I thought it was the type of thing you imagine and talk about.
But then we heard a real voice.
We were so upset.
But I had to keep working on the sappho.
I think it was a very strange picture.
It was fun.
That's the picture you sold this time.
First of all, let's start with this,
The first one over there, the one at the Museum of Sound, is a for-sale photo.
I didn't know there was such a way to take pictures.
Yes, there is.
If you find something like this, you should generally use it.
In the recent Instagram situation, there are such things.
It's there.
And here is the frog shrine.
It's a frog.
The tiles that were there before.
It's so cute.
I want everyone to take a picture of this because you'll notice it.
Please do.
Frogs.
Frogs are everywhere.
The shrine was overflowing with frogs.
It was wonderful.
It's closed.
See you again next time.
Bye bye.
This is Chikkake from Orca News.
Yes, I'm Chikkake from Killer Whale News. I'm Chikkake of Killer Whale News, and I'll start with our news.
We are a collaboration unit of Coming Flavor and Team Killer Whale, both of which are based in Nagoya.
We are releasing our first single "Eyes Pride" as "Shachifre", a collaboration unit of Coming Flavor and Team Orca,
We are going to hold a special event to celebrate it in Shibuya tomorrow and the day after tomorrow.
Yay!
We will be divided into three groups for the event,
We will be divided into three groups for the event, and you will be able to talk with them a lot,
I hope you will get to know each other well and come to see us.
A lot. I said a lot.
I've said a lot of things.
That's how many people have come. I've met a lot of people.
You are so kind.
You want to talk a lot, don't you?
You're so kind.
And April 18?
April 20?
20 days!
April 20 in Nagoya, and May 18 in Shinjuku,
We will also have a live performance of Chachifre.
Yay!
We will of course have each live performance, but we will also have something that you can only see here,
Please come and see them. We are looking forward to seeing you there.
We are looking forward to seeing you.
And our big event of the summer,
This year, we will be holding our big summer event, Killer Whale Summer, at Nagoya Castle.
Yay!
I can't believe that we will be able to live the "one, one, one life" at Nagoya Castle this year!
We've been dreaming about it for a long time, and we can't believe we're going to be able to do it!
It's been our dream to do a one-man show at Nagoya Castle, and to do it outdoors in the summer with Shirt-sama.
It's also the place where this all started, right?
I hope many people will come to this place and I want to make a lot of noise, so please come and join us on the 22nd of March.
That's all for the news in the car!
Thank you very much!